I Believe in Unicorns is a drama film directed by Leah Meyerhoff.
Feeling awkward and isolated, an imaginative and strong-willed teenage
girl runs away from home with an older punk rock drifter.
Davina, played by Natalia Dyer.
Sterling, played by Peter Vack.
Cassidy, played by Julia Garner.
Clara, played by Amy Seimetz.
Toni, played by Toni Meyerhoff.
Girl on scooter, played by Johnny Sequoyah.
I Believe in Unicorns is a 2014 American independent coming-of-age
romantic drama film written and directed by Leah Meyerhoff.
The film stars Natalia Dyer, Peter Vack, Julia
Garner, Amy Seimetz and Toni Meyerhoff.
The film was released on May 29, 2015, by Gravitas Ventures.
The tone is emotional.